看到你平安到达我就放心了
I'm glad to see you made it safely
酒店怎么样
How's your hotel?
虽然不是我住过的最佳"最佳西方酒店"
It's not the best Best Western I've been to,
但算得上
but I'd say it's...
我住过的第三佳"最佳西方酒店"吧
the third best Best Western I've been to.
我懂你的感觉
I know how you feel.
我家附近的百思买[最值买]也只是第三值
The Best Buy by my house is only the third best Best Buy.
它的确有最值买的东西
They have the best buys,
但光有最值买的东西并不足以
but having the best buys isn't the only thing
让一家"最值买"荣登最值的"最值买"
that makes a Best Buy the best Best Buy.
那最值"最值买"怎么样才能担起这头衔呢
What makes a best Best Buy the best Best Buy?
这问题问得好
Mm, that's a great question.
我喜欢它们开在墨西哥快餐店旁
I like when they're next to a Chipotle.
好了  我该去把行李拿出来了
Okay, well, I should unpack.
好的
All right.
好好享受神经生物学大会吧
Enjoy the neurobiology conference.
我会的
I will.
我...  真希望你也在这里
I... wish you were here.
参加神经生物学大会吗
At a neurobiology conference?
这话也太损了吧
What a mean thing to say.
好吧  那我很庆幸你不在这里呢
Okay, I'm glad you're not here?
真好  每次只要我一教
Aw, you always know just what to say
你就会把话说到我心坎里
after I tell you what to say.
再见啦  谢尔顿
Good-bye, Sheldon.
再见
Bye.
好消息  各位
Oh! Good news, gentlemen.
艾米这周末去参加会议
Amy's at a conference this weekend,
这就代表你们有荣幸能娱乐本皇
which means I'm available to be entertained, hmm.
也就是现在年轻人说的
As today's youth might put it:
谁有兴趣来"谢"主隆恩啊
Who wants to get their Sheld-on?
我跟妮妮要为家里的重新装修做准备
Bernie and I are getting the house ready for the remodel.
我们很乐意有你来帮忙
We could always use an extra pair of hands.
一听就烂透了  拉杰呢
That sounds awful. Raj?
这周末我已预定好使用太空望远镜控制室
Uh, I've got time booked in the telescope room all weekend
来搜索流浪行星
scanning for rogue planets.
欢迎你跟我一起去
You're more than welcome to join me.
列入考虑  莱纳德呢
That's the one to beat. Leonard?
你别来烦我就"谢"天谢地了
Oh, if anything, I'm trying to get my Sheld-off.
看来冠军得主已经出炉  恭喜你
Well, then it looks like we have a winner. Congratulations.
先提醒你  那只是单纯坐在电脑前
Well, I should warn you, it's just looking at data
看好几小时的数据而已
for hours and hours on a computer screen.
已经选你  别再诱惑我了
Uh, stop selling it, kid. You won.
翻译：流星的流弊赛太公  恒星的恒心YY猫
别扭大菜
今天好吗
How was your day?
不太好
Oh, not good.
还是没能见到加洛医生
Still couldn't get in to see Dr. Gallo.
医生吗
A doctor?
你的病可别有传染性啊
Well, I hope you're not contagious.
我这周末要去太空望远镜控制室
I've got a weekend in the telescope room
我可是为此兴奋了将近有三分钟呢
I've been excited about for almost three minutes.
我没生病  是工作啦
I'm not sick. It's for work.
有一个医生拒绝见任何医药销售员
There's this doctor who refuses to see any sales reps.
我试着要见这医生好几个月了
I've been trying to get in for months.
你有穿那件
Well, did you try wearing the shirt
我说上班穿太骚的衣服试试吗
I said was inappropriate for work?
那是个女医生  不过...
Well, the doctor's a woman, but...
穿了  毕竟"直弯"试过才知道
yes, because you never know.
她是什么医生
What kind of doctor is she?
精神科医生  怎么了
Um, a psychiatrist. Why?
那你假装自己是病人去预约呢
Well, what if you make an appointment as a patient?
那你就有机会跟她谈啦
Then you'll get to talk to her.
他们已经知道我是医药销售员了
Yeah, they already know I'm a pharmaceutical sales rep.
那如果是莱纳德假装病人去预约
Oh. What if Leonard made an appointment
先帮你铺好路呢
and tried to lay some groundwork for you?
这个主意有意思
That's interesting.
我才不要假装病人去看精神科医生
I'm not gonna make a fake appointment with a psychiatrist.
我要假装有啥毛病呢
What would I say is wrong with me?
-自尊低落  -社交焦虑
- Low self-esteem. - Social anxiety.
性生活不安全感
Sexual insecurity.
你们说得都不是真的
None of that is true.
否认现实  亲爱的  毛病多得很啊
Uh, denial. See, sweetie, the list goes on and on.
这也太扯了吧
That's just crazy.
我去了对你有什么帮助啊
How would my going in there even help you?
不知道啊  你可以跟她聊天  谈到药时
I don't know. You could talk to her, and maybe if it comes up,
就顺势问问她有没听过我公司的药
you could ask if she's heard about the drug.
万一被抓到怎么办
What if I get caught?
-害怕失败  -缺乏自信
- Fear of failure! - Lack of confidence!
有点怂逼
Kind of a wuss!
行  我去
Fine, I'll do it.
但不是因为他们的话  是因为我爱你
But not because of them, because I love you.
谢谢
Thank you.
-软柿子   -没骨气
- Pushover. - Spineless.
两天前就交代去买牛奶  到现在都还没买
Still hasn't bought milk even though I told him two days ago!
真是爽翻天了
That was incredible.
的确
It was.
要是斯图尔特不在就更好了
I just wish Stuart wasn't around
我们想多大声就能多大声
so we didn't have to be so quiet.
对啊
I know.
而且这家伙看日本色情动画时
It's not like he returns the favor
也不知放大声点回报咱们
when he watches his Japanese porn cartoons.
你们俩有空吗
You guys got a minute,
还是还在事后抱抱
or are you still cuddling?
有事吗  斯图尔特
What is it, Stuart?
我能进来吗
Can I come in?
稍等
Hang on.
要不要我赶他走
Should I send him away?
不用  没事
No, it's okay.
谢谢你  妮妮
Thanks, Bernie.
你要干嘛
What's up?
我知道你们很快要重新装修了
Uh, well, I know the remodel is coming up,
所以我想让你们方便作业
so I thought I'd make it easy on you guys
就出去找房子
and find my own place.
我真没想到今晚能"好事"成双啊
I thought I was done getting lucky tonight.
所以你计划什么时候搬
So, when are you thinking of moving?
其实我已经找好一间公寓了
Uh, actually, I already found an apartment,
所以过几天就搬
so in a couple of days.
好吧
Oh. Okay.
真舍不得你走咩
Sorry to see you go?
谢谢你们这些日子来的照顾
Okay, well, thank you guys for everything.
我真的非常感谢
I-I really appreciate it.
不用客气
You're very welcome.
怎么了
What?
我只是从来没在你们醒着的时候进来过
Hmm, I just have never been in this room while you're awake.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
确保望远镜的摄像机白场已平衡
Uh, making sure the telescope's camera is white-field balanced.
那现在呢
What are you doing now?
还在确保望远镜的摄像机
Still making sure the telescope's camera
白场已平衡
is white-field balanced.
了解
Oh, I see.
那现在呢
How about now?
现在在确保望远镜的摄像机白场已平衡
Now I'm making sure the telescope's camera is white-field balanced
以及后悔你没有一本彩色填色本
and wishing you had a coloring book.
我可以帮上忙啊
Well, I can be helpful.
给我点事情做做嘛
Give me something to do.
告诉你  有一次我爹带我去上班
You know, my father took me to work once,
才十分钟我就发现了
and in ten minutes I figured out
到底是谁从收银机里偷钱
who'd been stealing from the cash register.
就是我爹
It was my father.
我爹丢了工作
Yeah, Dad lost his job,
但是他老板给了我根软糖冰棒
but Mr. Hinckley gave me a Fudgsicle.
行  你想要来点事做是吧
Fine, you want something to do?
这硬盘里有搜集了大约六个月的数据
There's about six months of data on this hard drive.
你何不过一遍这些数据  看能否发现
Why don't you go through it and see if you can spot
有任何规律或异常呢
any patterns or anomalies.
好的  我这就去
Yep, I'm on it.
你看我们
Hey, look at that!
印度阿三把电脑工作外包给白人佬
An Indian guy outsourcing a computer job to a white fella.
随便怎么样
Yeah, okay, whatever it takes
只要能让你忙个数小时就行了
to keep you busy for a few hours.
找到一个
Found one.
不可能
No, you didn't.
那有好几百万数据点呢
There are millions of data points there.
可是你看  一个光学瞬态
But, look, an optical transient.
好吧  可能真的有东西
Yeah, maybe that is something.
-你怎么发现的  -其实不难啦
- How did you find that? - It wasn't difficult.
就像质数在你眼里自动就是红色的
You know how when you see prime numbers, they appear red,
孪生质数是粉红色
but when they're twin primes,
而且闻起来像汽油  你懂我的意思吗
they're pink and smell like gasoline?
不懂
No.
可能我与众不同吧
I guess I'm a special boy.
有时候当一个男孩与众不同
You know, sometimes when a boy is special,
他会得到一根软糖冰棒
he gets a Fudgsicle.
而且味道尝起来像光速
Which, by the way, tastes like the speed of light.
非常感谢你能临时抽空见我
Thank you for seeing me on such short notice.
乐意效劳
Ah, it's my pleasure.
我很好奇
I'm curious,
你和贝弗莉·霍斯塔特博士是亲戚吗
are you related to Dr. Beverly Hofstadter?
她是我母亲  你认识她吗
Uh, she's my mother. You know her?
不  不认识本人
No, not personally,
但我读过她所有的书
but I have read all of her books.
那你对她的认识比我还深
Well, then you know her better than I do.
不见得
Well, I'm not so sure about that.
但我可以告诉你
But I can tell you I do not agree
我完全不同意她育儿的那套理论
with her theories on child rearing at all.
是咩
Really?
你是不是觉得那一套过于冷漠残酷
Any chance you find them cold, cruel and unsuitable
并不适合天真无邪  想快乐生活的小男生
for innocent little boys who just want to be happy?
我不想妄加评论
Well, I didn't want to say it...
不不  请评论  唱出来
No, no, say it. Sing it.
租一架飞机  写在天空
Rent a plane, write it in the sky.
听起来你对她
Sounds like you're holding on
一直心怀怨念  怒气满满啊
to quite a bit of anger towards her.
不  我已经努力克服不少怨念
Oh, no, I-I've worked through a lot of that stuff;
-现在好多了  -那就好
- I'm better now. - Good for you.
你知道她从不让我庆祝自己的生日
Do you know she never let me celebrate my birthday
就因为我的出生是她的成就  不是我自己的吗
because being born was her achievement, not mine?
真是让人心碎
That's heartbreaking.
是吧
Right?
直到今天  我还每年给她寄卡片
To this day, I send her a card every year
里面还附上一点钱
with a little money in it.
一旦这房子只剩咱俩
You know, once we get the house back to ourselves,
我们就能在任何一个房间"搞浪漫"啦
we can be romantic in any room we want.
好棒  我终于可以让你知道洗衣房在哪了
Great. I can finally show you where the laundry room is.
天啊  谁能想到
Boy, who would've thought
当时你让我搬进来照顾你妈
when you asked me to move in and help take care of your mom,
结果两年后的今天我才走
I'd still be here two years later?
-没人有想到  -没人
- Nobody thought that. - No one.
都结束了
Well, that's it.
是啊
I guess so.
感觉好奇怪
This is weird.
是啊  一个成年人即将搬进他自己的公寓
Yeah. A grown man moving into his own apartment.
真是疯狂的年代  回见
Crazy times. See ya!
别管他
Ignore him.
他只是用幽默来表达他现在...
He's just using humor to express how...
有多开心
happy he is.
没关系  我知道他爱我
It's okay. I know he loves me.
你说是就是啦
Sure he does.
你安顿好了记得告诉我们
Well, let us know when you're all settled in.
我会的
I will.
我对你们真的感激不尽
And I really can't thank you guys enough.
我们的荣幸
Our pleasure.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye.
他走了
He's gone!
我们从车库开始搞吧
Let's start in the garage!
好了  一旦我们接收到下一张图像
Ok, so once we received the next image
把它跟我们之前搜集的作对比
and compare it to the ones we've already collected,
就能知道我们发现的是什么了
we'll know what it is that we found.
或许是日鞘闪烁的光
Ooh, perhaps it's a Heliosheath scintillation.
也可能是外海王星天体
It could be a trans-Neptunian object.
也许是一个新星球
Maybe it's a new planet.
不太可能  但可能是矮行星
Unlikely, but it could be a dwarf planet.
只要它有健康的重力
Well, as long as it has a healthy gravity
该有的卫星都有  我就开心了
and all its moons, I'll be happy.
好了  最后一张图片来了
Okay, the final image is coming in.
我们发现的天体是...
And the object we discovered is...
拜托了
Come on,
爸比需要一颗可以施行铁拳政策的宜居星球
Daddy needs a livable planet he can rule with an iron fist.
一颗中型小行星
A medium-sized asteroid.
就这样吗
That's it?
真普通
How common.
简直就是太空菜单上的鸡柳啊
That's the chicken fingers on the menu of space.
我挺喜欢鸡柳的
I kind of like chicken fingers.
我也是  我只是想不到其他比喻了
Yeah, me, too. I was stuck for a metaphor.
别这样嘛  一颗中型小行星
Come on, a medium-sized asteroid
也是一项有意思的发现啊
is still an interesting discovery.
我想它的确有可能会跟地球撞上
I suppose it could end up on a collision course with Earth
毁掉一切生命体
and destroy life as we know it.
你我梦想天差地远
You dream different than me.
它还挺可爱的
It is kind of cute.
的确  我们还能给它起名字哦
Yeah, it is. And you know we get to name it.
我们最好选一个没人会取笑的名字
We better choose a name no one can make fun of.
赫歇尔爵士取的名字就坑死天王星了
Sir Frederick William Herschel didn't do Uranus any favors.
-进展如何  -很顺利
- Hey, how'd it go? - Oh, great.
加洛医生太棒了
Dr. Gallo is terrific.
我一直觉得没有安全感
You know, I-I've always been insecure
因为没人关心我要说什么
that no one cares about what I have to say,
-但她让我觉得...  -没人关心这个啦
- but she made me see... - Yeah, no one cares.
你到底有没有帮我说话
Did you help me out or not?
好吧  我听你这句话
Okay, n-now, what I'm hearing
感觉像你嫌我有时用太多时间
is that you feel that I sometimes take too long
来表达自己的感受
to express myself,
你希望我说话简单明了
and you wish I'd be more succinct.
我之所以说出来是因为
You're only hearing that because
你听不到我翻白眼的声音
I cannot roll my eyes any louder.
好吧  在我们谈了我跟我妈的问题后
All right, well, after we talked about my issues with my mother--
也没太深入  就聊了她怎么毁了我的人生
nothing too deep, just how she ruined my life--
我告诉她你和你的药
I told her about you and your drug;
她说她很乐意见你
she said she'd be happy to meet you.
真的吗
Really?
你是史上最棒的老公了
Oh, you're the best husband ever!
那你下周会跟我去神秘博士大会吗
So you'll go to the Doctor Who convention with me next week?
会吧
I guess.
这次我听出你白眼翻到外太空了
Oh, I actually did hear your eyes roll that time.
天啊  斯尔图特从来没打扫过房间吧
Boy, when was the last time Stuart cleaned this place?
肯定是
No kidding.
好了  某物要被我吸进吸尘器了
Oh, okay, I'm about to suck something up.
你觉得这东西听起来像什么
What do you think this object sounds like?
我不想再玩猜是乐高  脚趾甲  还是药丸的游戏
Howie, I don't want to play Lego, Toenail or Pill anymore.
我们该怎么运用这个房间呢
So, what do you think we should do with this room?
我在考虑弄成家庭影院或游戏房
Well, I was thinking a home theater or a gaming room--
就像一个男人窝
you know, like a man cave.
为什么就不能是女人窝呢
Why can't it be a woman cave?
只要内含家庭影院  电子游戏机
As long as it has a home theater, a video game system
而且禁止你入内
and you're not allowed in it,
你想叫什么都行
you can call it whatever you want.
我是说真的啦
I'm being serious.
你觉得我们该怎么做
Well, what do you think we should do?
我不知道
I don't know,
或许弄成家庭办公室或...
maybe a home office or...
瞧
Look.
我们带斯尔图特去园游会时  他赢的泰迪熊
The teddy bear Stuart won the night we took him to the fair.
他当时超级兴奋
He was so excited.
是啊
Yeah.
不管他们怎么绞尽脑汁
You know, no matter how hard they tried,
都猜不出来他几岁
they could not guess his age.
下次我看见他时给他吧
I'll give it to him next time I see him.
-他走了之后有和你联系吗  -没有
- Have you heard from him since he left? - No.
以为他安顿好了  就会给我们打电话呢
You'd think he would've called once he got settled in.
也许他比较忙吧
Hmm. Maybe he's busy.
忙到电话都打不了吗
Too busy to call?
他用我的会员账号
He wasn't too busy
上网追《燃情克利夫兰》就有空吗
to binge-watch Hot in Cleveland with my Hulu password.
怎么回事
What is happening?
我们是在想他吗
Are we missing him?
没有  这种感觉才不是想他
No, that's not what this feeling is.
是吗
Is it?
当然不是  他总能逼疯我们
Of course not. He drove us crazy.
还记得有一次你准备烤个派
Like when you were gonna make that pie
结果斯图尔特把蓝莓都吃光了
and Stuart ate all the blueberries.
他还想赖账  可是牙都吃紫了
And he tried to deny it, but his teeth were all purple.
还挺可爱的
That was pretty cute.
是啊
Yeah.
靠  我们真是在想他
Ew, we are missing him!
我在想  或许我们可以
So I was thinking, maybe we can come up with a name
把我俩名字拼起来给小行星命名
for the asteroid by combining our names.
这个主意好
That's a great idea.
我想到了
I've got it.
我们就叫它...库珀
We'll call it... Cooper.
这哪里是我们俩的名字
How is that both our names?
库是取自"库"萨帕里  而珀取自库"珀"
"Koo" from Koothrappali and "per" from Cooper.
好吧  所以是我的那个"库"吗
Yeah, s-so it's, like, Kooper with a "K"?
不要了  你说得对  这主意太蠢了
Nah, you're right, that's dumb.
莱纳德  好消息
Oh, Leonard, great news.
我们一起发现了一颗中型小行星
We discovered a medium-sized asteroid together.
太棒了
Wow, that's amazing!
我今天心情也很不错
I'm in a pretty great mood today myself.
行吧  看来你要把话题转到你身上了
Okay. Guess we're gonna talk about you now.
是的  因为加洛医生让我意识到
Well, we are, because Dr. Gallo made me realize
我是值得好好对待的人  我的感觉也很重要
that I'm a worthwhile person and that my feelings matter.
我是免费从一张猫咪海报上学到
I learned that for free from a cat poster,
不过你开心就好
but good for you.
好的  说回我这里
Okay, back to me.
我发现了一颗小行星
I discovered an asteroid,
现在我可以给它起名了
and now I get to name it.
等等  不是我们吗
Wait, what happened to us?
现在重点不是我们
Now, this isn't about us,
而是怎样才算对小行星好
this is about what's best for the asteroid.
你们准备给它起名叫什么
What are you thinking of naming it?
我还没有定下来
I haven't settled on anything yet.
我们还没有定下来
We haven't settled on anything yet.
棒棒棒  猫咪海报  一边挂着去
All right, way to go, Cat Poster. You hang in there.
用你们女朋友的名字命名不是更好吗
You know what'd be nice? Name it after your girlfriends.
显得你们多在乎她们啊
Show them how much you care.
这个主意妙啊
That is a great idea.
完美
It's perfect.
表面好像很浪漫
It appears romantic,
其实只是太空里的一块石头而已
but it's really just a rock in space
还能让我以后都不用愁情人节了
that gets me out of Valentine's Day forever.
你有什么想法  把她们名字拼起来吗
So, uh, what were you thinking? Combine their names?
这样可以
I like it.
我们就从艾米的名字里取"艾"字
Yeah, we'll take the "A-M" from Amy and, uh,
然后艾米丽的名字里取"米"字
the "Y" from Emily.
那就是"艾米"啊
That's just Amy.
正是如此  瞧我们合作无间啊
Exactly. See how well we work together?
在双盲试验中
And in double-blind studies,
此药被证明对治疗各种焦虑症
Placinex proved extremely effective in treating
都极其有效
all kinds of anxiety.
说个有意思的事  实验室里的人
Actually, funny story-- the boys in the lab
很焦虑食品药物管理局会不批这个药
were worried about getting FDA approval for Placinex;
就开始吃这药  然后就再也不担心了
they started taking it, stopped worrying.
懂了
Got it.
你有什么问题想问吗
Uh, do you have any questions?
就一个
Just one.
当你让你老公扮成病人
When you made your husband pretend to be a patient
好让你有机会跟我接触时
so you could get access to me,
你当时在想什么呢
what were you thinking there?
我是指关于药的问题
I just... meant a question about the drug.
我知道你是什么意思
Yeah, I know what you meant.
先把这个放在一边
Let's put that aside for a minute
聊聊为什么你会嫁给莱纳德
and talk about why you married Leonard.
我不想
I don't wanna.
这是一个被专横霸道的女人养大
Here is a man raised by an overbearing woman
从性格形成时期
who completely dominated
就各方面被彻底压制的男人
every aspect of his formative years.
你认为他是希望
Do you think
一直维持这种关系
he's perpetuating that relationship
才会找野蛮女友当伴侣的吗
by seeking out a partner like you?
我以前总是穿无袖背心
You know, I used to wear tank tops a lot.
这个卖点非常吸引顾客
That was a big selling point.
谢尔顿  怎么了
Hi, Sheldon. What's up?
好消息  你是颗行星了
Good news. You're an asteroid.
请你告诉我这句该怎么接
Uh... please tell me what to say next.
看来我得解释一下
Perhaps I should explain.
在跟库萨帕里一起工作的时候
While working with Koothrappali,
我们发现了一颗小行星
we discovered an asteroid,
我以你的名字给它命名了
and I named it after you.
谢尔顿  谢谢你
Sheldon, thank you.
这太浪漫了
That's so romantic.
那拉杰什怎么办
But what about Rajesh?
他同意让你用这名字吗
He was okay with you choosing the name?
确实花了一些时间磋商
Well, it took a little negotiating,
最后我将他说服了
but I wore him down.
小行星的命名权给我们
Uh, we get the asteroid,
但如果我们生了孩子
and if you and I have children,
都得取名叫拉杰什
they all have to be named Rajesh.
全都要叫这名吗
All of them?
连女儿都要
Even the girls.
好吧 我知道现在该说什么了
Okay, I think I know what to say now.
当我们的卧室
How can I not sound like his mother
被星战玩具塞满  我怎么可能不变身他妈
when our entire bedroom is filled with Star Wars toys?
你跟人上床的时候
I mean, have you ever had sex
有试过被伍基人毛绒玩具盯着看吗
with a stuffed Wookiee watching you?
我念大学的时候是七十年代
I went to college in the '70s;
那时候大家都不刮毛
it was a hairier time.
所以我的答案是 是的
I'm gonna say yes.
就算我像他妈  也是被他逼的
You know, if anything, he's turning me into his mother.
我当医药销售之前是个演员
Before I did pharmaceutical sales, I was an actress.
相当优秀的演员
You know, I was pretty good.
那种邻家女孩型  但很性感
You know, girl-next-door type, but hot.
有"搞"头那种
Doable.
我不仅成了莱纳德的妈
And not only am I Leonard's mother,
还有这个老小孩跟我们一起住  叫谢尔顿
but we have this man-child living with us named Sheldon.
莱纳德确实说过他很多事
Oh, Leonard talked a lot about him.
我之前不确定他是否真实存在
I wasn't sure if he was real.
他的真实程度就跟
Yeah, he's as real as the fine I get
我上厕所多用手纸被他罚款一样真
when I use too much toilet paper.
你烦心事真是够多啊
Wow, you really do have a lot on your plate.
是的
I do.
说真的   莱纳德说得对
You know, Leonard's right.
跟你聊天特别有帮助
Talking to you is really helping.
很高兴能帮上忙
Oh, I'm glad.
一张治疗焦虑症的处方
You know, you might also benefit
对你也是大有益处
from a prescription for anxiety.
好的 你觉得有用就好
Okay, if you think it'll help.
拜托不要给我开我公司的药
Oh, just don't make it Placinex.
我不需要突然暴怒想杀人的副作用
I do not need sudden fits of homicidal rage.
我想你
I miss you.
我也想你
I miss you as well.
不敢相信我想念斯图尔特
I can't believe I miss Stuart.
我大概只是想念过去简单的生活
I guess I just miss when life was simpler.
加油  莱纳德
Go, Leonard! Go, Leonard!
记住姑娘们  你的开心你做主
Remember, girls, you decide what makes you happy,
而不是由你压抑情感的老妈来定
not your emotionally withholding mothers.
加油  莱纳德
Go, Leonard! Go, Leonard!
Go, Leonard! Go, Leonard! Go, Leonard!
我真的好想念这样
I really miss this.